First they took his daughter. Now they're coming for him.
Taken 2 is a action, crime, thriller film directed by Olivier Megaton.
In Istanbul, retired CIA operative Bryan Mills and his wife are taken hostage by
the father of a kidnapper Mills killed while rescuing his daughter.
Bryan Mills, played by Liam Neeson.
Kim Mills, played by Maggie Grace.
Lenore St. John, played by Famke Janssen.
Sam Gilroy, played by Leland Orser.
Bernie Harris, played by D. B. Sweeney.
Mark Casey, played by Jon Gries.
Taken 2 is a 2012 French action-thriller film directed by Olivier Megaton and starring Liam
Neeson, Maggie Grace, Famke Janssen, Rade Šerbedžija, Leland Orser, Jon Gries, D.B.
Sweeney, and Luke Grimes.
It follows retired CIA officer Bryan Mills as he ends up with his family in Istanbul, where he is kidnapped, along
with his ex-wife, by the father of one of the men he killed while saving his daughter two years earlier.
It is the sequel to the 2008 film Taken and the
second installment in the Taken trilogy.
Released on 3 October 2012 in France by EuropaCorp and 5 October 2012 in the United States by 20th Century Fox, the film grossed over $376
million at the box office, making it the highest grossing installment of the trilogy, but received negative reviews from critics.
A third film, Taken 3, was released on 9 January 2015.
The film explores themes of kidnapping, fbi,
turkey, police chase, teenage daughter.
The tone is intense.